

JULIANA Y. LEE

WEB DEVELOPER

San Francisco, CA · <u>lee.julianay@gmail.com</u> · 781-510-6599 · <u>www.itsjlee.io</u>

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Dedicated full stack web developer with a background in outpatient pharmacy and pharmacy operations. Team oriented thinker with the experience to prioritize high-volume tasks, the ability to solve multifaceted issues and a passion for building and optimizing interactive, user-friendly and feature-rich websites and web applications.

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Nov 2019- Sep 2020 Web Development Program

Harvard

Sept 2008- Dec 2010 Pre-Medical Studies

Univ. of Massachusetts Boston

Sept 2002- Aug 2008 Psychology Major (B.S.), Biology Minor

CORE COMPETENCIES

- Strong attention to detail
- Expert in customer relations and services
- Cross collaboration
- Avid learner

SKILLS

- CSS, HTML, Javascript, jQuery, AJAX, JSON
- · React JS, Angular, Vue
- MongoDB, Express, Node
- AWS
- Git

SPECIAL INTERESTS

- Android/iOS development with React Native
- Web game development
- Kalimba tablature

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CareerFoundry

Full stack web development student

Nov 2019- Sep 2020

- Build functioning SPA web applications with focus on client-side and server-side web technologies
- Demonstrate mastery of the full MERN stack, including REST APIs, web server frameworks, middleware modules, databases, business logic, authentication and data security
- Achieve proficiency in user interface, testing and debugging with web development best practices
- Implement agile methodologies, such as user stories, story points, kanban boards to manage projects from start to finish.

UMass Memorial Specialty Pharmacy

Worcester, MA

Prior Authorization Specialist, CPhT, MS Department

Dec 2014- May 2016

- Delivered integrated patient care for specific disease states
- Strengthened patient relations by communicating directly and assisting in medication compliance
- Actively participated in process improving initiatives by identifying trends, resolving problems, recommending new approaches and implementing changes to our patient care model
- Applied research and investigative information to enable strategic decision making by our team and to better customer service standards

CarePlus Pharmacy

Boston, MA

Certified Pharmacy Technician, CPhT

Dec 2012- Dec 2013

- Provided mail order specialty medication therapy and consultation for patients within the New England area
- Developed an extensive knowledge on Medicare, funding organizations and health insurance companies/policies
- Strategized drug-inventory management to eliminate waste and back orders

CVS/Pharmacy

Boston, MA Dec 2005- Oct 2013

Certified Pharmacy Technician, CPhT, Lead Technician

- Educated and dispensed medication to patients in an outpatient setting
- Facilitated improvements to data entry, doctor calls, managing drug inventory, drug cycling counts, prescription filling, inter-pharmacy transfers and patient care initiatives
- Oversaw technician schedules and directed operational duties
- Established excellent customer service standards by resolving product/ service complaints and followed up to ensure resolution